Yes, sir.
Oh, there's something about that story.
Hmm?
Yeah.
Oh.
No, it's okay.
What's this?
Yes, sir.
Let's do our best.
They'll think it's you again.
If I say something like that...
They'll really think that about me.
That's enough.
Not you again.
I'll be here all my life, doctor.
You.
Oh!
Hey!
Hi!
You again?
I'm Mirei Hoshina.
No, no, no, no... That's why.
I'm looking forward to your live delivery this week.
Please do.
Let's start the recording.
I'd like to start.
Okay.
Well, I'm often in Hoshi.
When I hear about your travels...
I hear about your travels, and the things you've done, and from my point of view, what I want is someone who's very active.
I hardly move at all compared to you, so no, no, no, there are masters too.
I don't go to the mountains... but I thought... you're great too...
I'm sure you're great, but your friends are great too.
Do you always go with a group of friends?
Not just a few.
Not a few people?
I went to Korea this time...
I'm always doing Akita Bunko with Ebichu.
In Akita.
I went with an announcer I got along with at the station there.
I see you're in the industry.
I had summer vacation plans with him, so we came together.
Is the announcer also a very good player?
No, not really, but I think she does her footwork a lot better than I do.
There's still someone above you.
I think there are.
I guess when you have someone like that around, you get pulled in.
That's actually who I went to Korea with.
Wow....
Welcome home!
But isn't home with Sarpong too?
What?
He never moves.
I mean, I feel like I've been to a lot of places.
If you ask me, you're on the lowest level.
I'm probably one of those people who either moves or doesn't.
I think I'm somewhere in the middle.
The master?
You're probably around here.
Lower than that?
What about me?
If you want it, you're in the upper echelon.
You're really powerful, aren't you?
Yes, I'm sure.
That's why...
I think it's just a small thing.
Yes.
Because, you know...
If there was a chance, everyone would go, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
When someone says something...
Like, "Oh, that's nice.
After today, people usually go out for a drink.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But if I'm alone, I'll die.
That's already true.
Right?
That's right.
When you're sick, you don't feel like it.
Oh, well, well, well, well...
So I'd like to make a move, after all.
How's that?
Master, let's go to Korea.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's great. I can't even picture it.
Say, "Let's go to Korea!
Yes, that's right.
I buy all kinds of cosmetics and stuff.
I became beautiful.
And then they put oil on their beds again.
Too much oil," she said.
So I think it's important to be with people, including friends.
It's amazing how much they influence you.
That's right.
No, no, no, well, well, well, that's why, you know.
Well, well, well...
I would like to write to you.
I'd like to write to you.
Let's go to this corner, shall we?
Let's go to this corner...
Imagine living things!
It's amazing! So strong and weak!
Weak and strong!
Weakness!
Applause for the strong and weak!
So, let's see...
I got it.
Mr. Beer from Kanagawa Prefecture.
Thank you.
Er, creation of creatures.
Yes, sir.
It's already amazing. The name is amazing.
May I?
Yes.
Monochrome diarrhea.
Black and white diarrhea? Maybe it's mono-diarrhea. It's a soccer ball. It's a soccer ball.
I don't know if it is monochrome diarrhea or black-and-white diarrhea, I don't know the intonation, but there is a creature with such a name.
The other day, at a creature creation event, there was a stink bug? Turtles? I don't remember what it was called.
I don't remember what it was called, but it was something like "Nanzai-zaa. Like Kaiser. I was watching the broadcast with my parents, and we were talking about that, and we said "Hekusamushi" in Yamagata.
Especially, stinkbugs are called by different names in different areas.
They have many names. Yes, yes, yes. That's why they are so hated. So that's how it is.
Like a stinkbug. In the provinces, you know, all sorts of things. Like Gaidar Gaidar. Gaidar Gaidar. Gaiderguider-Guider-Guizer. What was it? What was it?
Black and white kick. Black-and-white kick. Black-and-white kick. Black-and-white kick. Wow, I can't imagine it at all.
Well, I've probably never seen it. I don't think so. Maybe the real thing. No, I haven't.
Black-and-white kicking. Just as a hint, or for your information, I heard that there are not so many in Japan, except in zoos.
I was surprised to hear that.
Yes, that's a very good hint.
This is it!
I can't write it, I have to rewrite it.
I'll rewrite it.
Master, you're late!
It's just that there aren't many of them in Japan.
Isn't it great that you can tell?
It's a black-and-white kick.
Black and white?
I don't know.
I had an intonation.
There's something about that zoo.
Of course they're there.
I think so.
You've seen them, right?
I've seen them.
But I don't think it's something you'd normally see around here.
Maybe.
Can we change the schedule a little bit?
Sure, sure.
There it is, there it is... right under my nose.
It's just a change of direction for something I've been working on.
Don't be surprised by what you get.
I'm supposed to be good at this.
But come to think of it...
But now that I think about it... we've been doing this Sarpon thing for a whole year now, and this is our second year.
I'm getting used to it... and we're getting used to it... his drawings... and I'm happy.
I'm used to the horror of it, or rather, I was used to the horror of it at first, so... yes, yes, yes, yes.
I think it's a lot more decent.
I think he's pursuing that rareism in his work.
Hoshino, you ready? Okay, let's start with Hoshino. Black and white kick.
What? What's this? It's a penguin.
A little bit.
Is it a lady?
She looks like a lady from Ocatta.
You look like an old lady dressed up as Doraemon.
A penguin.
You're right. It's more black-and-white.
It's all I've got.
Okay, my black-and-white slice, here it is.
A panda!
That's right! A panda!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Pandas!
Well, well, well. I'm sure it's a panda.
I'm sure it's a panda.
Why is it so party-ish?
I was going to draw a turtle first.
Turtle?
I was going to draw a turtle.
Yu told me there were turtles at the zoo.
In black and white?
Black and white, so a panda.
I see.
I was going to draw a turtle.
But, you know, doesn't this one look like it could be in the same place? This character.
Well, well, well... sure.
Why is it like this?
Sasa.
Oh, there you are.
Why do you have a piece?
No, I can't hold it.
It's a double peace.
I can hold it.
I just don't know how to hold it.
How to hold it? What kind?
The sasa.
Sasa?
Oh, you tried to hold the sasa? You couldn't hold it.
No, you can't hold it like this. You can't put your hand on it.
You can hold it like this. You can't hold it like this.
You can't hold it like this. If you hold it like this...
Is this a foot? Yes, feet. That's why I drew the turtle in the first place.
You mean from above? First, you draw a turtle from above?
We thought, "Well, this is what it looks like," and then he turns around with a panda, and then he draws it from the top.
No, no, no, no, it's amazing, isn't it?
But it looks like this... no, I didn't see it... please stop it, Hoshida-san... look at this...
This is amazing! I wonder why...
What is it?
I don't know... this... what can I call it... this...
You're writing something different from what I'm thinking... maybe it's this... or this... or this... or a lot of this... or this... or this... or this... or this.
It's just that this time, the tortoise went home first, and this is just how it turned out.
You've been doing it every time, seriously... and it's just a matter of taking what I think is right... and writing it down.
This is the only way or the only currency. Then it's not so easy to understand what's going on in your brain, is it?
Gario's not so great anymore, is he?
Isn't it amazing?
On the contrary...
Something's going on inside his brain...
He's saying too much.
By the way, black-and-white kicking is... not a bird.
Well, it's just like the penguins say, well, if you put it like that, it's right.
I'm buying it, mostly I'm buying it, mostly I'm buying it, mostly I'm buying it, mostly I'm buying it, mostly I'm buying it, mostly I'm buying it, mostly I'm buying it
I went to the zoo.
I go to the zoo and there are many things I have to do, but the way they cry makes them run around like a metal sound.
Like at the big field, or like hitting gold or metal
They make a can-can-can-can-can-can-can sound.
It's like a sound of metal.
I want to hear it.
Then there are a lot of animals on the ship.
I haven't paid attention to them.
I guess I haven't paid attention to it since today.
I've been thinking...
For example, I was trying to draw a panda and I thought my drawing skill was not good enough.
No, no, no, no.
I already have enough artistic ability.
I see.
It's strange what replayed in my brain.
So this is a panda.
It's a perfect panda for you.
It's a panda.
Pandas have, like, a border, right?
There's no border.
Borders are still changing.
Is everyone okay?
Everybody okay?
No, no, no, no, no.
Perfect.
Well, well, well, well.
That's what I'm talking about.
And I got a letter for you, too.
Yes.
I'll take these back now. Let's see if we can get to the letters.
Thank you very much.
It's peeling.
Great paintings. - They're amazing.
He's a very talented artist. Mr. Shiritsu Ebisu Jugoku, Shinjuku-ku, Tokyo.
He's a company employee. Thank you.
Master Riah, my part-time worker, Ebichu-chan.
Thank you very much.
Last week I was in Shibuya
I was in Shibuya last week and I got a pair of running shoes and a pair of running sunglasses for a short play.
I heard he got inspired by it.
So he drew this picture.
He drew this picture.
Wow!
It's a picture of...
Eva's...
Gendou?
That's right!
He became Gendou Ikari.
Iwanokatani...
So that's what this is about!
Wow!
I'm Evangelion.
The Master.
You're the third child or something?
A fourth child?
Against the Master
"You're useless as a regular part-timer.
He said...
And he said...
I can definitely imagine him running around with this thing on.
I'm at mark 16.
That's cool. - Yeah.
I've done a lot of driving at the Famien.
I was there...
They make me run.
They think I'm fast, so they make me run.
Nonoka... it was like watching herself as a kid again.
She seemed to be having a lot of fun running.
She said it's the best time for her, too.
"It's going to take me as long as ever.
I was feeling nostalgic.
I'm saying this is the best part... but he's running so fast, I'm afraid I'm going to blow him off.
I see.
Is there a birthday party going on today?
I see... KTZEPP Yokohama
I see. So you're probably wearing it.
Please tell me if you know if he's wearing it or not.
Maybe he's running.
And if you go to a significant place, you might wear the sunglasses.
I'm not Naoko Takahashi, but...
No, no, no, no... but... you're very powerful.
I don't know... Sway-Bon
There's this pose, isn't there? Yes, there is. It's the same pose as the one he does when he runs to catch the ball.
It's exactly the same pose as the special pose of running to catch the water.
And I was thinking... you look a little like me...
I like it a lot.
I love what you just said.
The firepower is amazing!
And one more thing...
I'll draw Ayakase again.
Ayakase was sent to me as a subject for creating a creature, but...
I saw the picture of the creature, but it was too plain.
I saw the picture, but it's so plain that I didn't think it would be good to show it.
But the story is interesting.
I see.
What's the creature's name?
Lia Elegance.
Wow!
What's the name of the creature? That's me! What do you think it is, by the way? Laia Elegance.
Butterfly or something? Well, not a butterfly, but something like that?
Moth! I'm thinking more like a butterfly. Butterfly? Butterfly? Butterflies fly, right? Yes, they do.
What do they fly towards? Butterflies? Flowers?
Yes, they are.
There's a chrysanthemum plant called Lia elegans.
Yeah, it's a chrysanthemum.
Yeah, and the language of flowers is "elegance.
Yeah.
Perfect.
Yeah, and it's actually... and I've written about it in Ayacazo, but...
It's a rather ordinary-looking plant.
It's really a tree.
It doesn't really have any special characteristics.
It's not very distinctive.
Rhea Elegance.
I'm good at it.
Raiya Elegance is attached.
Masked Liar.
Is it here?
Oh, yeah.
You're right. It's so normal.
It is normal.
You have to wear this.
Liar Elegance, please.
It's yellow. It's something.
What can I say?
It's special.
It didn't feel like it was making any kind of noise.
It didn't sound like anything.
I don't like it when it's my imagination.
I don't know, I don't want to put elegance on it.
I'm sure you're right.
I'm normal, so I don't want you to.
From my point of view.
From the nose
I wish you would have chosen a more modest name.
Nose-wise.
Why not say "Elegance"?
That's true.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Well, well, well
I also thought Ayaka was amazing
Her eyes...
Her eyes are a little dazed.
She does that a lot, doesn't she?
Do you? You do?
Yes, I do.
Really?
It's like you're looking a little bit far away.
Oh, my God.
Like when you're waiting.
You do?
I do.
Oh, my God.
You scared me.
He's staring at me.
I have to do it right.
You're really good at this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, well, well, well.
That's how it was.
If you have any more letters, please send them to us.
Yes.
Yes, sir.
So...
Okay, then, Mr. Live Delivery.
I almost sneezed.
I was trying to hold it in all the way through.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Sarpong, they say you're normal.
I've got to give it a touch of elegance.
That's classy.
Thank you.
Classy, isn't it?
I'm Sarpon.
You look like a madam.
You're still wasting your time.
Well, well, well...
Speaking of hot news...
Since we're doing a live broadcast...
What's the hottest news?
What's ours?
We?
What news?
We.
What?
What are you talking about?
Who are you talking to?
Humans?
What?
What do you mean?
I'm talking to some bird or something.
Did they really do something to you?
Where's your free time these days?
That's not something a celebrity would say. I'm really bored.
And yet it's so easy to apply for the exam to get certified as a financial planner... it's frustrating.
I see.
You know now? That's why I'm traveling.
That's why... I'm also making my debut in Canada over the next two weeks.
I'm glad you're here.
That you come here so often.
Maybe you won't come back.
I don't know.
Until we meet again.
Don't say such a sad thing so suddenly.
Like a graduation ceremony.
Like a graduation ceremony
It was fun.
But... for those of you who are watching the live broadcast, I don't want to give you any advance notice, but... this week...
This week... the pictures... well...
I know a lot of people are going to be mad at me, but...
Please help me pay for my trip.
Thank you very much.
There's a lot of bad photos.
I wonder if it's true... that photo of the lunch box... is it that bad... is it that bad?
I thought...
I thought "Is it that bad?
The live photo, you know, on the air.
Sarpo's inner self is really coming out.
Yeah, there's something about the condensation that makes me want to give him a Pulitzer Prize or something for that picture.
Oh, there is such a thing?
A photograph is great because it captures a moment, a moment.
Yes, that's right.
It's not just an ordinary landscape, it's a moment of emotion.
What?
That's great!
I'm so happy.
That's wonderful.
I want to show you a picture of a squid, and two pictures of a squid, and two pictures of a squid.
I'm looking forward to seeing them, they're really interesting.
Unlike the squid pictures, there's also a selfie of me.
Seiya on the master's computer No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, it's great!
Another angle of the squid!
So, I hope you'll all come to the organ.
It's coming in about two weeks.
I hope you'll enjoy it.
That's all I have to say.
I'll see you next week at 8:00 or 8:00 p.m.
I'll see you at 8:00 p.m.
Thank you very much for this week.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.